myonlinearcade.com 2017-10-24

# My Online Arcade Privacy Policy

**MYONLINEARCADE.COM  PRIVACY POLICY**

MyOnlineArcade is committed to providing an entertaining, fun and educational service. MyOnlineArcade respects the privacy concerns of visitors to Myonlinearcade.com. MyOnlineArcade does not target its website or services to under 13 year olds, but does take measures to help protect those that happen to be under 13. We take measures to help children protect their privacy while online. For example, we do not ask children to disclose more personal information than is necessary for them to participate in a particular activity.

**Information we collect**  
We may log IP addresses and/or drop cookies and/or flash cookies to prevent abuse of our website and or to provide and or to enhance services. Email addresses of persons under 13 are not stored. They are encrypted into an unrecoverable format using a one way hash. Of those users who choose to register we collect date of birth, username, password and email address of users 13 years and older. For registered users non personal information may be collected related to use of the website and website services and activities such as high scores, game rankings, league rankings, game challenges, avatars, etc.

**Information that is reasonably necessary**  
MyOnlineArcade does not require persons under 13 years of age to disclose any more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity as a condition of participation.

**How we use the information**  
We do not retain any personal information beyond the time it is needed. We may use information to ensure that users are in compliance with our terms. Persons over 13 years of age authorize us to send them email notifications related to MyOnlineArcade products and services including the MyOnlineArcade Newsletter. MyOnlineArcade may disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with MyOnlineArcade’s property, visitors, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.  
We may sometimes use non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our website, to personalize our visitors' experience or to offer products, programs and services. We may also use this information in the aggregate to analyze website usage, as well as to offer products, programs, or services.

**Collection of Information and Third-Parties and Sponsors**  
We do not disclose personally identifiable information of users under 13 years of age to third parties. We use DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies and MyOnlineArcade may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this website and other websites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Third parties and or MyOnlineArcade may be placing and reading standard and or flash cookies on your browser and machine, or using web beacons to collect information on the website and in the course of ads being served. We may also share the anonymous information that we collect from you with our business partners or clients so that they may improve their services. Third parties such as advertisers, games companies and or developers may ask for information from you which would be governed by the privacy policy of those other companies in which case they should provide adequate disclosure of their privacy policies to you. We may use anonymous information that we collect from you to improve our services and or to help serve advertising to you. You may manage or opt out of your standard cookies via your web browser.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Security**  
We have implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy is part of MyOnlineArcade’s main Terms and Conditions which you agree to by accessing the MyOnlineArcade.com website and/or services. You agree that MyOnlineArcade may change this Privacy Policy and the main MyOnlineArcade Terms and Conditions at any time. Our current Privacy Policy will be posted here: 

_<http://www.myonlinearcade.com/privacypolicy>_

which is part of our Terms and Conditions posted here: 

_<http://www.myonlinearcade.com/termsandconditions>_

. Our contact email for questions is 

_[[email  protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#0d7e787d7d627f794d60746263616463686c7f6e6c6968236e6260)_

.
